ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials /4283/001 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials
1998-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Fleron, Lou Jean
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4283/001 AV
3.67 cubic feet
3.7 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
9267626
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, January 06, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 22, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
Fleron, Lou Jean; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. b Extension and Public Service Division; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
9267626
- Jack Williams - 1-26-2000, 1 (Box 1)
- Fentnor - 11-17-1998, 1 (Box 2)
- Kumbiega - 6-15-2000, 1 (Box 3)
- Tony Strusa - 2-7-2000, 1 (Box 4)
- Warren Bartel - 1-27-2000, 1 (Box 5)
- 1-21-2000, 1 (Box 6)
- Arvin / Jeff - Jones/Paycheck -- Powertrain - 1-6-2000, 1 (Box 7)
- Charlie Humphrey - 1-26-2000, 1 (Box 8)
- D. Hayes - CWA 1169 - 1-21-2000, 1 (Box 9)
- Massarot & Johnson - 2-22-2000, 1 (Box 10)
- Pionta/Banks - 12-19-1999 -- R. Lipsitz/P. Wilcox, 1 (Box 11)
- Jim Voye - 2-25-2000, 1 (Box 12)
- Martin Oscadal - 2-10-2000, 1 (Box 13)
- George Kollor - 1-25-2000, 1 (Box 14)
- Baych - 1-7-2000, 1 (Box 15)
- Lipsitz - NAFTA - 2-15-2000, 1 (Box 16)
- Boody & Kirsch - 1-11-1999, 1 (Box 17)
- Empire S. Steel - 8-25-2000, 1 (Box 18)
- Wetmore - 11-19-1999, 1 (Box 19)
- O. O'Donnell - 8-30-2000, 1 (Box 20)
- Jack Williams - Part 1 - 1-26-2000, 1 (Box 21)
- Moog - 8-22-2000, 1 (Box 22)
- Herb Fulson - 3-29-2000, 1 (Box 23)
- Futureview w/Kevin Donovan - 1-21-2000 [Both sides + notes(written) of Chris Whalen, 1 (Box 24)
- Ron Lucas - 11-8-1999, 1 (Box 25)
- Warren Bartel - 1-27-2000 (part 2), 1 (Box 26)
- Barrett Scott - TOPS; Lipsitz, Jones, Kroetsch // 12-7-1999 [1 of 2], 1 (Box 27)
- TOPS Markets -- M. Jones; R. Lipisitz; C. Kroetsch; J. Barrett; M. Scott - 12-7-1999 [tape 2 of 2], 1 (Box 28)
- Klinko Kipsitz - Teamsters -- Jones/Kroctsch -- 12-6-1999 [1 of 2], 1 (Box 29)
- Klinko - Teamsters; Lipsitz-Teamsters - 12-6-1999 -- Jones/Kroctsch [2 of 2], 1 (Box 30)
- Unlabeled VHS tape, 1 (Box 31)
- Educational Curriculum Kit / Niagara Mohawk - New York Power Authority // Nikola Tesla: The Genius Who Lit the World Tesla Memorial Society; The 100th Anniversary of Long-Distance Electric Transmission Niagara Mohawk Power Corp., 2 (Box 31)